JUAN FELIPE BETANCUR CANO

Front-end Developer

Medellín, Colombia • +57 (300) 521 9306 • juanfelipebetancurcano@gmail.com LinkedIn: /in/juanfelipebetancurcano

SUMMARY

Front-end developer with 7 years of experience in the design and development of solutions. My experience ranges from project analysis to development and implementation. I have a positive mindset and ability to learn quickly, which has allowed me to adapt to diverse work environments and face technical challenges effectively.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end Developer, Flyr

Mar 2023 - Present

- Develop user interfaces using technologies such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Angular, ensuring a fluid and responsive user experience.
- Contribute in the development of an important migration, focused on improving user experience, information optimization and performance.
- Participate in the technical analysis of the requirements, working as a team to evaluate the best alternative and define the technical specifications, designing the most appropriate solution for each request.

Software Developer, Pragma

May 2021 - Jan 2023

- Analyze and design technical solutions that met the specific needs of a financial project.
- Participate in project migration to new technology, assisting with the transition process and ensuring effective integration with existing systems.
- Contribute to the development of a credit system that allowed people with little credit history to obtain easy and immediate financing.

Front-end Developer, Konecta

Jan 2020 - Apr 2021

- Participate in the analysis, technical design and implementation of customer requests.
- Contribute in the development of functionalities that improved the time management of the customer.
- Lead the technical analysis and development of an important functionality that significantly reduced the size of the database when migrating information to files, which allowed a remarkable optimization in the performance and storage of the system.

Software Developer, Websaas

Mar 2019 - Jan 2020

- Develop major software features regarding to functional requirements.
- Provide application support, managing and resolving technical issues to ensure system availability and stability.
- Design and implement applications with a focus on user experience, ensuring functionality and performance.

- Analyze, design and develop new functionalities, ensuring that they meet business requirements and improve system efficiency.
- Provide technical support for applications, identifying and fixing bugs, ensuring stability and optimal performance of solutions in production.
- Design, develop and maintain relational databases, optimizing their structure and queries to ensure fast and efficient access to information.
- Design and implement hybrid mobile applications, focused on user experience, adapted to iOS and Android platforms, and optimized for efficient performance.

EDUCATION

Associate's Degree

SENA, 2018

• Analysis and Development of Information Systems.

ADITIONAL INFORMATION

- Technical skills: HTML, CSS, Angular, JavaScript, TypeScript, Ionic, Git.
- Languages: Spanish, English B1 (currently studying).
- Soft skills: Effective communication, teamwork, adaptability, creativity, responsibility.